Finding Aid for Michigan Historical Records Survey records, 1936-1942
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Survey forms of 1987 Survey of Records in Counties and Municipalities
  - Municipal Surveys (Box 47)
Calendar of the Baptist Collection of Kalamazoo College, Kalamazoo, Michigan
Calendar of the John C. Dancy Correspondence, 1898-1910
Cemetery Records, Jackson County, Michigan
Directory of Churches and Religious Organizations: Greater Detroit, 1941
Land Records, Grantors, Kent County, Michigan
Master Index to Records in Volumes ABC - LI, Briefed from Wayne County Records of Register of Deeds, volumes A to 104
Probate Records from Archives of Wayne County, Michigan
Alger County
Alpena County
Baraga County
Bay County
Calhoun County
Cheboygan County
Delta County
Genesee County
Iosco County
Iron County
Jackson County
Marquette County
Muskegon County
African Methodist Episcopal Church, Michigan Conference
Church of the Nazarene, Michigan District Assembly
Protestant Episcopal Bodies, Diocese of Michigan
Protestant Episcopal Church, Diocese of Northern Michigan
Protestant Episcopal Church, Diocese of Western Michigan
The Roman Catholic Church, Archdiocese of Detroit
Salvation Army in Michigan